(Previously) Gaysorn, from now on,
(سابقاً) Gaysorn، من الآن فصاعداً،
I won't let anything hurt you ever again.
لن أدع أي شيء يؤذيك مرة أخرى.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Last night, Gaysorn's fragrance filled the entire house.
في الليلة الماضية، ملأ عطر جايسورن المنزل بأكمله.
How are we going to extract it?
كيف سنستخرجه؟
I need clothes with more of Gaysorn's scent on them.
أحتاج إلى ملابس تفوح منها رائحة جايسورن أكثر.
Come on!
تعال!
The faster your heart beats, the more you'll sweat.
كلما زادت سرعة نبضات قلبك، زاد تعرقك.
Hey, you! Let me wipe it for you.
يا أنت! دعني أمسحها لك.
I also want to know...
أريد أن أعرف أيضاً...
why Mr. Scent had Kusuma's staff collect Gaysorn's sweat-wiped cloth.
لماذا طلب السيد سينت من موظفي كوسوما جمع قطعة القماش المبللة بالعرق من جايسورن.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Why can't I make it? Why?
لماذا لا أستطيع فعل ذلك؟ لماذا؟
Please eat something.
من فضلك تناول شيئاً.
I'm not hungry yet.
لست جائعاً بعد.
Hey.
يا.
It's been four years already.
لقد مرّت أربع سنوات بالفعل.
It's been four years of you trying to come up with the Bussaba scent.
لقد مرّت أربع سنوات وأنت تحاول ابتكار عطر بوسابا.
You've been hidden in this lab and not going anywhere else.
لقد تم إخفاؤك في هذا المختبر ولن تذهب إلى أي مكان آخر.
Our company is in trouble when nobody is looking after it.
شركتنا في ورطة عندما لا يهتم بها أحد.
Also your son is about to go to school.
كما أن ابنك على وشك الذهاب إلى المدرسة.
What? You can't handle that?
ماذا؟ ألا تستطيع التعامل مع ذلك؟
When I can bring back the Bussaba scent,
عندما أستطيع استعادة رائحة بوسابا،
everything will get better.
كل شيء سيتحسن.
Come on.
تعال.
I told you
أخبرتك
when we can bring back the s…scen…
متى نستطيع إعادة المشهد...
Hey!
يا!
Who's there? Come here and help!
من هناك؟ تعالوا إلى هنا وساعدونا!
"Flower Boy" (Episode 5)
"فتى الزهور" (الحلقة 5)
This?
هذا؟
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
This is a cloth to wipe your sweat, you remember?
هذه قطعة قماش لمسح العرق، أتذكر؟
Why is it in the bag?
لماذا هو في الحقيبة؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
I am as curious as he is.
أنا فضولي مثله تماماً.
Why do you ask a courier from Kusuma
لماذا تطلب من ساعي بريد من كوسوما
to come and collect this with Gaysorn's sweat on it?
هل سيأتي ويأخذ هذا وعليه عرق جايسورن؟
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Are you a pervert?
هل أنت منحرف؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
I can answer it for him since I'm his ex.
بإمكاني الإجابة نيابةً عنه لأنني حبيبته السابقة.
He never collects anything from his boyfriend,
لا يأخذ أي شيء من صديقه أبداً،
he didn't even care.
لم يكن يكترث حتى.
What is your plan exactly?
ما هي خطتك بالتحديد؟
Scent?
رائحة؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I need an explanation.
أحتاج إلى تفسير.
Fine, I will tell you.
حسناً، سأخبرك.
But you two can't tell anyone about this,
لكن لا يمكنكما إخبار أي شخص بهذا الأمر،
okay?
تمام؟
I just want to extract your scent to make a perfume.
أريد فقط استخلاص رائحتك لصنع عطر.
Huh?
هاه؟
Hey,
يا،
I'm sorry for not telling you sooner.
أعتذر لعدم إخبارك في وقت سابق.
We'll talk at home.
سنتحدث في المنزل.
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
Gaysorn!
Gaysorn!
Gaysorn.
Gaysorn.
Please listen to me.
أرجوكم استمعوا إليّ.
I have a reason for doing this.
لدي سبب لفعل هذا.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
that you said you would go home after finding your mom?
أنك قلت إنك ستعود إلى المنزل بعد العثور على والدتك؟
I've thought about it and I realized
لقد فكرت في الأمر وأدركت
I couldn't live without your scent.
لا أستطيع العيش بدون رائحتك.
I want to preserve your scent
أريد أن أحافظ على رائحتك
and that's it.
وهذا كل شيء.
You don't have to do that.
ليس عليك فعل ذلك.
I wont do it anymore.
لن أفعل ذلك بعد الآن.
If you don't like it, then I won't do it.
إذا لم يعجبك الأمر، فلن أفعله.
I don't know how long we'll stay together like this.
لا أعرف إلى متى سنبقى معاً على هذا الحال.
I want to see you smile,
أريد أن أراك تبتسم،
I want to see you laugh,
أريد أن أراك تضحك،
I want our memories will be filled with good feelings.
أريد أن تكون ذكرياتنا مليئة بالمشاعر الطيبة.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Hey,
يا،
you said that
قالوا ذلك
you didn't know how long we would stay together.
لم تكن تعلم كم من الوقت سنبقى معًا.
If you can choose,
إذا كان بإمكانك الاختيار،
how long would you like me to stay?
كم من الوقت ترغب أن أبقى؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
لا أريدك أن تذهب إلى أي مكان.
I want keep smelling your scent like this.
أريد أن أستمر في استنشاق رائحتك هكذا.
You don't have to develop a perfume of my scent.
لستَ مضطراً لتطوير عطر يحمل رائحتي.
Women from Mudan
نساء من مودان
will gradually
سوف تدريجياً
lose their scents when they're pregnant.
تفقد روائحها عندما تكون حاملاً.
On the contrary, scents from men
على العكس من ذلك، روائح الرجال
will continue to be like this
سيستمر الوضع على هذا النحو
until we are old.
حتى نكبر في السن.
Then I will keep smelling you until you're old.
سأظل أشم رائحتك حتى تشيخ.
Pinky swear for making up.
أقسم لكم على المصالحة.
Gaysorn.
Gaysorn.
I will keep searching for your mom for you,
سأستمر في البحث عن والدتك من أجلك.
No matter how long it takes,
مهما طال الأمر،
I will find her for you.
سأجدها لك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
My brain is fried after smelling so many perfumes.
لقد أرهقني استنشاق كل هذه العطور.
My phone?
هاتفي؟
Where is it?
أين هي؟
Scent?
رائحة؟
What voice messages?
ما هي الرسائل الصوتية؟
Sun,
شمس،
Gaysorn found out about us developing a perfume.
علمت شركة Gaysorn بأمر تطويرنا للعطور.
And he is not fine with it.
وهو غير راضٍ عن ذلك.
So I decided
لذلك قررت
not to continue with Mudan scent.
عدم الاستمرار في استخدام عطر مودان.
I'm sorry that you've spent so much time on this.
أنا آسف لأنك قضيت الكثير من الوقت في هذا الأمر.
You can abort the mission.
يمكنك إلغاء المهمة.
I will talk to Uncle about it.
سأتحدث مع عمي بشأن ذلك.
What did he say?
ماذا قال؟
Uncle?
عم؟
What did Scent say?
ماذا قالت سينت؟
He sent voice messages.
أرسل رسائل صوتية.
- Well, call him back! - Okay, okay.
- حسناً، اتصل به مجدداً! - حسناً، حسناً.
I…
أنا…
He turned off his phone.
أغلق هاتفه.
It can't be.
لا يمكن أن يكون ذلك.
We promised the investors to launch the new scent.
لقد وعدنا المستثمرين بإطلاق العطر الجديد.
Uncle… look.
عمي... انظر.
I prepared a few scents just in case.
لقد جهزت بعض العطور تحسباً لأي طارئ.
Nothing can beat the scent from the Mudan.
لا شيء يضاهي رائحة مودان.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
What are you cooking?
ماذا تطبخين؟
I'm cooking soup.
أنا أطبخ حساءً.
You know how?
هل تعرف كيف؟
I'm watching the clip.
أنا أشاهد المقطع.
Can I help you?
أيمكنني مساعدتك؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
- Ow! - Be careful.
- آخ! - انتبه.
I think it's easier to buy the soup.
أعتقد أن شراء الحساء أسهل.
Nope.
لا.
We're living together and I want to help you out.
نحن نعيش معًا وأريد مساعدتك.
How is it? Is it good?
كيف هو؟ هل هو جيد؟
So good.
جيد جداً.
This is chef-cooking level.
هذا مستوى طهي الطهاة المحترفين.
Really?
حقًا؟
Really.
حقًا.
I will check on that, you should rest.
سأتحقق من ذلك، عليك أن ترتاح.
You left me such dangerous messages
لقد تركت لي رسائل خطيرة للغاية
and then you turned off your phone?
ثم قمت بإغلاق هاتفك؟
How could you do that to me?
كيف تجرؤ على فعل ذلك بي؟
So you came all the way to my house to call me out?
هل أتيت إلى منزلي خصيصاً لتوبيخي؟
Damn right I am!
بالتأكيد أنا كذلك!
You told me to abort the mission and you left me a bomb.
أمرتني بإلغاء المهمة وتركت لي قنبلة.
You told me that you would talk to you uncle.
أخبرتني أنك ستتحدث إلى عمك.
Hey, I said that I would talk to him,
أجل، قلتُ إنني سأتحدث معه.
- which means that I am about to… - No, you can't.
- مما يعني أنني على وشك أن... - لا، لا يمكنك ذلك.
You have to talk to him now.
عليك التحدث إليه الآن.
He is so furious.
إنه غاضب جداً.
I've never seen him being this furious before.
لم أره غاضباً إلى هذا الحد من قبل.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
I am dead serious.
أنا جاد تماماً.
Hey.
يا.
Who's here?
من هنا؟
It's Sun. He needed to run some errands but he left.
إنه يوم الأحد. كان عليه أن يقضي بعض المشاوير لكنه غادر.
Are you tried of the city view?
هل مللت من منظر المدينة؟
Why did you ask me?
لماذا سألتني؟
Do you want to look at the sea?
هل ترغب في النظر إلى البحر؟
The sea?
البحر؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
The sea, like I showed you the picture of.
البحر، كما أريتك صورته.
Really? I do.
حقاً؟ نعم.
Let's go. We should go now.
هيا بنا. يجب أن نذهب الآن.
Why do we have to hurry?
لماذا علينا أن نستعجل؟
So we will get there faster.
لذا سنصل إلى هناك بشكل أسرع.
Scent.
رائحة.
Uncle?
عم؟
- I'm about to… - Is this Gaysorn?
- أنا على وشك أن... - هل هذا غايسورن؟
I have something to talk to him about.
لديّ موضوع أريد التحدث معه بشأنه.
I will get straight to the point.
سأدخل في صلب الموضوع مباشرة.
Did you know that
هل تعلم ذلك؟
Scent wanted to develop your scent?
هل ترغب في تطوير عطرك الخاص؟
I told you
أخبرتك
that he wasn't okay with that.
أنه لم يكن موافقاً على ذلك.
We won't continue the project.
لن نواصل المشروع.
Why's that?
لماذا؟
What about your dad? What are you going to do?
ماذا عن والدك؟ ماذا ستفعل؟
Uncle?
عم؟
Don't you feel sorry for his dad?
ألا تشعر بالأسف تجاه والده؟
Does my scent have something to do with him?
هل لرائحتي علاقة به؟
Well…
حسنًا…
You should leave my dad out of this.
يجب أن تستبعد والدي من هذا الأمر.
Why?
لماذا؟
If Gaysorn realizes how bad your dad's condition is,
إذا أدرك جايسورن مدى سوء حالة والدك،
I'm sure he will help us.
أنا متأكد من أنه سيساعدنا.
What's wrong with Scent's dad?
ما المشكلة في والد سينت؟
You should leave.
يجب أن تغادر.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
This is Scent's dad,
هذا والد سينت،
he is my older brother.
هو أخي الأكبر.
His dad tried to develop a perfume with the Mudan scent.
حاول والده ابتكار عطر برائحة مودان.
But he couldn't succeed.
لكنه لم ينجح.
He was so stressed, he couldn't eat or sleep
كان يعاني من ضغط نفسي شديد، لدرجة أنه لم يستطع الأكل أو النوم.
until he got a stroke.
إلى أن أصيب بجلطة دماغية.
And he became like this.
وأصبح على هذا النحو.
We thought that if Dad could smell Mudan's scent again,
كنا نظن أنه إذا استطاع أبي أن يشم رائحة مودان مرة أخرى،
he would recover and be back to normal.
سيتعافى ويعود إلى وضعه الطبيعي.
You think it's possible.
أنت تعتقد أن ذلك ممكن.
Hey.
يا.
This is Scent's friend.
هذا صديق سينت.
He is from Mudan.
هو من مودان.
He has the same scent that you want.
لديه نفس الرائحة التي تريدينها.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
It is the scent
إنها الرائحة
that is more fragrant than all of flowers in this world.
إنها أكثر عطراً من جميع الزهور في هذا العالم.
- Dad? - What?
- أبي؟ - ماذا؟
Hey!
يا!
Dad?
أب؟
Bro?
أخ؟
What is wrong with him?
ما به؟
- Dad? - What?
- أبي؟ - ماذا؟
What is wrong with him?
ما به؟
I don't know. He's never been like this.
لا أعرف. لم يكن هكذا من قبل.
Hey!
يا!
- Hey! - Dad?
- مهلاً! - أبي؟
Everyone, please leave.
أيها الجميع، من فضلكم انصرفوا.
Please wait outside.
يرجى الانتظار في الخارج.
Dad?
أب؟
- Please leave, everyone. - Dad?
- من فضلكم انصرفوا جميعاً. - أبي؟
Wait outside, please.
انتظر بالخارج من فضلك.
Please, just go.
من فضلك، اذهب.
Sir, you need to breathe slowly.
سيدي، عليك أن تتنفس ببطء.
Sir?
سيد؟
You need to breathe slowly, okay?
عليك أن تتنفس ببطء، حسناً؟
Okay?
تمام؟
Breathe in, breathe out, slowly.
تنفس ببطء، ثم أخرج الزفير.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
لماذا لم تخبرني بذلك؟
I didn't want to tell you
لم أكن أريد أن أخبرك
because I didn't want to use it to pressure you.
لأنني لم أرغب في استخدامه للضغط عليك.
But now I know.
لكنني الآن أعرف.
If you're not okay with it, don't mind my uncle.
إذا لم تكن موافقاً على ذلك، فلا تهتم لأمر عمي.
You have power over your own scent and body.
لديك القدرة على التحكم في رائحتك وجسمك.
I don't want to make you feel uncomfortable.
لا أريد أن أجعلك تشعر بعدم الارتياح.
- Hello.
- مرحباً.
First of all, I would like to thank
أولاً وقبل كل شيء، أود أن أشكر
all of the representatives for joining the event.
نشكر جميع الممثلين على مشاركتهم في هذا الحدث.
Kusuma is a small company,
كوسوما شركة صغيرة،
we're lucky that we can produce perfumes which people love.
نحن محظوظون لأننا نستطيع إنتاج عطور يحبها الناس.
We produced only 100 bottles of the Bussaba perfume.
لقد أنتجنا 100 زجاجة فقط من عطر بوسابا.
Many of you might be wondering
قد يتساءل الكثير منكم
why we produced only 100 bottles.
لماذا أنتجنا 100 زجاجة فقط؟
It is because
ذلك لأن
the perfume is developed from its confidential signature scent
تم تطوير العطر من رائحته المميزة السرية
so we can produce only 100 bottles.
لذلك لا يمكننا إنتاج سوى 100 زجاجة.
More importantly,
والأهم من ذلك،
we will never develop this type of scent in the future.
لن نطور هذا النوع من العطور في المستقبل.
If you take a look inside the envelope,
إذا ألقيت نظرة داخل الظرف،
you will smell the sample of this scent.
ستشم رائحة عينة من هذا العطر.
We'd like you to experience how fragrant
نود أن تجرب مدى روعة العطر
Bussaba can be.
يمكن أن تكون بوسابا كذلك.
Please try.
يرجى المحاولة.
It smells so nice.
رائحتها جميلة جداً.
I've never smelled anything this nice before.
لم أشم رائحة جميلة كهذه من قبل.
Now, I'd like to introduce all of you
والآن، أود أن أقدمكم جميعاً
to auction our new perfume.
سنقيم مزاداً على عطرنا الجديد.
The auction session begins right now.
تبدأ جلسة المزاد الآن.
The starting price will be
سيكون السعر المبدئي هو
50,000 baht.
50,000 باهت.
Every bid will move up at least 10,000 baht.
سيرتفع كل عرض بمقدار 10000 باهت على الأقل.
The auction will start now.
سيبدأ المزاد الآن.
60,000?
60 ألف؟
70,000? 80,000?
70 ألف؟ 80 ألف؟
90,000?
90,000؟
100,000?
100,000؟
110,000?
110,000؟
- 200,000 - 200,000?
- 200,000 - 200,000؟
300,000?
300,000؟
It is 300,000 baht already.
لقد وصل سعره إلى 300 ألف باهت بالفعل.
400,000?
400,000؟
410,000?
410,000؟
500,000?
500,000؟
Does anybody want to bid more than this? 500,000 baht going once?
هل يرغب أحد في تقديم عرض أعلى من هذا؟ 500,000 باهت تُباع لمرة واحدة؟
How was he?
كيف كان حاله؟
He's fine. He was just too excited earlier.
هو بخير. لقد كان متحمساً للغاية في وقت سابق.
You're not the only one who got excited.
لستَ الوحيد الذي شعر بالحماس.
I was so excited too.
كنتُ متحمسة للغاية أيضاً.
Please wait, it won't be long
يرجى الانتظار، لن يطول الأمر
for our company to make a great comeback.
لكي تحقق شركتنا عودة قوية.
Hey,
يا،
let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where to?
إلى أين؟
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا، لنذهب.
Is it pretty?
هل هو جميل؟
It is.
إنها.
So pretty.
جميلة جداً.
Thank you for taking me here.
شكراً لك على اصطحابي إلى هنا.
What?
ماذا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This is what we do when we are at the beach.
هذا ما نفعله عندما نكون على الشاطئ.
You want to start a fight?
هل تريد أن تبدأ شجاراً؟
- You really want to? - Hey!
- هل تريد ذلك حقاً؟ - مهلاً!
Is it how we do it?
هل هذه هي طريقتنا في القيام بذلك؟
There are so many
هناك الكثير
beautiful places in this world.
أماكن جميلة في هذا العالم.
I will take you to them.
سآخذك إليهم.
You're releasing your scent again.
أنت تطلق رائحتك مرة أخرى.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
you are my whole world.
أنت كل عالمي.
You are my whole world, too.
أنت أيضاً كل عالمي.
Scent,
رائحة،
about your dad.
عن والدك.
- Do you want me to...? - It's fine.
- هل تريدني أن أفعل...؟ - لا بأس.
I've been thinking about it.
لقد كنت أفكر في الأمر.
My dad became like this
أصبح والدي هكذا
because he was obsessed with the Mudan scent.
لأنه كان مهووساً برائحة مودان.
If he smells the scent again,
إذا شمّ الرائحة مرة أخرى،
his condition could get worse.
قد تسوء حالته.
Where did your dad smell the scent of the Mudan people from?
من أين شمّ والدك رائحة شعب مودان؟
Our company launched a product with the Mudan scent.
أطلقت شركتنا منتجاً برائحة مودان.
Mudan-scented perfume?
عطر برائحة مودان؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I was so young.
كنت صغيراً جداً.
But I remember that
لكنني أتذكر ذلك
it was the scent that ignited the company to be well-known
كانت الرائحة هي التي أشعلت شرارة شهرة الشركة
until now.
حتى الآن.
I don't think
لا أعتقد
we called it Mudan perfume back then.
كنا نسميه عطر مودان في ذلك الوقت.
I think Dad called it
أعتقد أن أبي أطلق عليه هذا الاسم
Bussaba perfume.
عطر بوسابا.
Bussaba perfume?
عطر بوسابا؟
Where did you get the idea that Busaba was taken from a person's name?
من أين أتيت بفكرة أن اسم بوسابا مأخوذ من اسم شخص؟
It must be from a person.
لا بد أن يكون من شخص.
I have no idea, I didn't come up with it.
ليس لدي أي فكرة، لم أتوصل إلى ذلك.
Then who did?
ومن فعل ذلك إذن؟
If they could smell the scent from the Mudan people,
لو استطاعوا شم رائحة أهل مودان،
it meant that they must've been close to the group.
هذا يعني أنهم لا بد أنهم كانوا مقربين من المجموعة.
They could be the one coming up with the name.
ربما يكونون هم من يقترحون الاسم.
Pruek.
برويك.
Pruek came up with the name.
برويك هو من اقترح الاسم.
Pruek?
برويك؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
He was the company's perfumer
كان صانع العطور في الشركة
who developed the Busaba scent.
من قام بتطوير عطر بوسابا.
Where is he now?
أين هو الآن؟
Pruek is dead.
برويك مات.
How did he die?
كيف مات؟
He fell down the stairs.
سقط من على الدرج.
I couldn't help him when I saw his body.
لم أستطع مساعدته عندما رأيت جثته.
That's so sad.
هذا أمر محزن للغاية.
What about the others?
وماذا عن الآخرين؟
Did you see him with someone else?
هل رأيته مع شخص آخر؟
I heard that
سمعت ذلك
he was in a fight with his wife
كان في شجار مع زوجته
and his wife disappeared.
واختفت زوجته.
Hey,
يا،
what's on your mind?
ما الذي يدور في ذهنك؟
Hey, calm down.
مهلاً، اهدأ.
Don't lose hope.
لا تفقد الأمل.
I don't know…
لا أعرف…
I got this from the HR department.
حصلت على هذا من قسم الموارد البشرية.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Here. This is Pruek.
هنا. هذه برويك.
If he could smell my mom,
لو كان بإمكانه شم رائحة أمي،
it meant that he could be my dad.
هذا يعني أنه يمكن أن يكون والدي.
Do you want to prove it?
هل تريد إثبات ذلك؟
How?
كيف؟
I also got this.
حصلت على هذا أيضاً.
It's his address.
هذا عنوانه.
But it looks like it's been abandoned for so long.
لكن يبدو أنه مهجور منذ فترة طويلة.
Look at this house,
انظر إلى هذا المنزل،
I'm not sure if we can find anything.
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان بإمكاننا العثور على أي شيء.
We can try to look.
يمكننا أن نحاول البحث.
That's him.
هذا هو.
So this is his house for sure.
إذن هذا منزله بالتأكيد.
Look.
ينظر.
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
Mom.
أم.
See that?
أترى ذلك؟
That's you.
هذا أنت.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
The photo that your mom held
الصورة التي كانت والدتك تحملها
was a picture of you when you were inside of her.
كانت صورة لك عندما كنت داخلها.
So this man is really my dad?
إذن هذا الرجل هو والدي حقاً؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Look.
ينظر.
Your mom and your dad,
والدتك ووالدك،
they smiled so big.
ابتسموا ابتسامة عريضة.
They must be so happy to have you.
لا بد أنهم سعداء جداً بوجودك.
Is this really my family?
هل هذه عائلتي حقاً؟
Not yet. Nope.
ليس بعد. كلا.
Tell them it won't be anytime soon.
أخبرهم أن ذلك لن يحدث قريباً.
What's going on? What's wrong?
ما الذي يحدث؟ ما الخطب؟
It's about work. What's your emergency?
الأمر يتعلق بالعمل. ما هي حالة الطوارئ لديك؟
Scent and Gaysorn are still dating.
لا يزال سينت وجايسورن يتواعدان.
Did you stalk them?
هل كنت تتجسس عليهم؟
Nope, I mean…
لا، أقصد...
people saw them go to the sea together.
شاهد الناس ذهابهم إلى البحر معاً.
Gaysorn is weird.
Gaysorn غريب.
He knows that his boyfriend is a pervert,
هو يعلم أن صديقه منحرف،
who wants to extract his sweat to make a perfume.
من يريد استخلاص عرقه لصنع عطر؟
Still, he won't break up with him. He's not scared at all?
ومع ذلك، لن ينفصل عنه . ألا يشعر بالخوف على الإطلاق؟
Maybe they're both insane.
ربما كلاهما مجنون.
But
لكن
you think people's scent is that nice?
أتظن أن رائحة الناس جميلة إلى هذا الحد؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
Or he could use his scent for other purposes
أو يمكنه استخدام رائحته لأغراض أخرى
so that it will smell better?
حتى تصبح رائحته أفضل؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You need to stop obsessing about them already. Such nonsense.
يجب أن تتوقف عن التفكير بهم بشكل مفرط. هذا هراء.
Wait.
انتظر.
Why're you so moody?
لماذا أنت متقلب المزاج هكذا؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Is everything okay?
هل كل شيء على ما يرام؟
I gave an interview earlier
أجريت مقابلة في وقت سابق
about the new scents from Kusuma.
حول العطور الجديدة من كوسوما.
It's been a while and we haven't had anything yet.
لقد مر وقت طويل ولم نحصل على أي شيء حتى الآن.
The clients are asking for new scents.
يطلب العملاء روائح جديدة.
Nobody wants to stock the old perfumes.
لا أحد يرغب في تخزين العطور القديمة.
I've asked them so many times
لقد سألتهم مرات عديدة
and they said that they couldn't provide the date.
وقالوا إنهم لا يستطيعون تحديد التاريخ.
Hey,
يا،
why don't you ask them directly?
لماذا لا تسألهم مباشرة؟
Ask who?
من تسأل؟
Mekin? What the hell?
ميكين؟ ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
What's going on? Hey!
ما الذي يحدث؟ مهلاً!
Ray, are you crazy? What's going on?
راي، هل أنت مجنون؟ ما الذي يحدث؟
My dad isn't here anymore.
والدي لم يعد هنا.
And I don't know where Mom is.
ولا أعرف أين أمي.
We will find your mom no matter what.
سنجد والدتك مهما حدث.
But…
لكن…
Mudan people
أهل مودان
won't leave their mates,
لن يتركوا رفاقهم،
unless…
إلا إذا…
Hey,
يا،
stop with your negative thoughts already.
توقف عن التفكير السلبي.
What if she's already dead?
ماذا لو كانت ميتة بالفعل؟
Listen to me,
استمع لي،
even if you have nobody left,
حتى لو لم يتبق لديك أحد،
you still have me.
ما زلتُ معك.
I will be right by your side.
سأكون بجانبك.
I'll be with you,
سأكون معك،
when you laugh,
عندما تضحك،
or when you cry.
أو عندما تبكي.
I promise you that.
أعدك بذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
But you told me that
لكنك أخبرتني بذلك
Mudan people
أهل مودان
will not leave their mate,
لن يتركوا رفيقهم،
when they find them.
عندما يعثرون عليهم.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Tawan.
تاوان.
I want you to have this.
أريدك أن تحصل على هذا.
Duen?
هل يحتوي على ذلك؟
You gave my nephew a silver bracelet,
أعطيت ابن أخي سواراً فضياً،
does your dad know about this?
هل يعلم والدك بهذا الأمر؟
That's like you're proposing to him.
هذا أشبه بأنكِ تتقدمين لخطبته.
(In unison) Let's get married.
(بصوت واحد) هيا نتزوج.
(In unison) A girl asked Tawan to marry her.
(بصوت واحد) طلبت فتاة من تاوان الزواج منها.
Tawan.
تاوان.
Duen will be sad if you leave it like that.
سيحزن دوين إذا تركته على هذا النحو.
You should keep it.
يجب عليك الاحتفاظ به.
Mata, please give it back to her dad.
ماتا، أرجوكِ أعيديها إلى والدها.
I won't accept a silver bracelet from anyone,
لن أقبل سوارًا فضيًا من أي شخص.
except
يستثني
you.
أنت.
Just go.
انطلق.
[Call from Scent]
[مكالمة من سينت]
Hey,
يا،
where are you?
أين أنت؟
I ordered us some food.
طلبت لنا بعض الطعام.
Please set the table.
يرجى تجهيز الطاولة.
I'll be right back to have dinner with you.
سأعود حالاً لتناول العشاء معك.
I see. Sure.
فهمت. بالتأكيد.
I have something special for you.
لدي شيء مميز لك.
And I have something special for you too.
ولدي شيء مميز لك أيضاً.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
Right?
يمين؟
Yeah?
نعم؟
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
I love you.
أحبك.
I love you too.
أحبك أيضًا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Can I have a bouquet of red roses?
هل يمكنني الحصول على باقة من الورود الحمراء؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
There you go.
تفضل.
Why are you home so early?
لماذا عدت إلى المنزل مبكراً جداً؟
Gaysorn?
جايسورن؟
Is it a village?
هل هي قرية؟
Yes.
نعم.
This is Mata's and Tawan's house.
هذا منزل ماتا وتاوان.
And this is my house.
وهذا بيتي.
Your house?
منزلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Oh, then what about my house?
أوه، وماذا عن منزلي إذن؟
Actually, this is our house.
في الحقيقة، هذا منزلنا.
Can I live with you?
هل يمكنني العيش معك؟
Please?
لو سمحت؟
Please, please, please... let me stay with you.
أرجوك، أرجوك، أرجوك... دعني أبقى معك.
Okay.
تمام.
Then I'll help you decorate the house.
ثم سأساعدك في تزيين المنزل.
(Next Episode) Gaysorn, I'm really sorry.
(الحلقة التالية) جايسورن، أنا آسف حقًا.
But there's one thing I never lied to you about.
لكن هناك شيء واحد لم أكذب عليك بشأنه أبداً.
Our love is real, Gaysorn.
حبنا حقيقي يا غايسورن.
I don't love you anymore.
لم أعد أحبك.
My heart doesn't beat fast...
قلبي لا ينبض بسرعة...
and I don't have any fragrance left for you.
ولم يتبق لدي أي عطر لأقدمه لك.
Are you really going?
هل ستذهب حقاً؟
I'm worried about Gaysorn. It's been more than a month already.
أنا قلق بشأن جايسورن. لقد مر أكثر من شهر بالفعل.
So that means, when my mother came down, my father was already dead.
هذا يعني أنه عندما نزلت والدتي، كان والدي قد مات بالفعل.
Then who told your mother to come down?
إذن من طلب من والدتك النزول؟
It's over between me and Gaysorn!
انتهى الأمر بيني وبين جايسورن!
No! If he wants to know where his mother is...
لا! إذا كان يريد أن يعرف أين والدته...
he must bring the scent back in exchange!
عليه أن يعيد الرائحة في المقابل!